{"1": {"question": "What does the K in K387 stand for?", "correct": "KÃ¶chel", "incorrect": ["Keldorfer", "Kreisler", "Krenek"]}, "2": {"question": "What is the form of 1st movement of string quartet K. 387?", "correct": "Sonata Form", "incorrect": ["Ternary form", "Rondo Form", "Binary form"]}, "3": {"question": "What is the main Key of the 1st movement of String Quartet K. 387?", "correct": "G Major", "incorrect": ["D Major", "G minor", "F Major"]}, "4": {"question": "When did string quartets first appear?", "correct": "1760s", "incorrect": ["1734", "1670s", "1890s"]}, "5": {"question": "What instrument or instruments start the second subject of the exposition in Mozart's String Quartet in G Major, K. 387, 1st Movement?", "correct": "2nd Violin", "incorrect": ["1st Violin and 2nd Violin", "1st violin and Cello", "Viola"]}, "6": {"question": "Who did Mozart dedicate his String Quartet K. 387 to?", "correct": "Joseph Haydn", "incorrect": ["Franz Schubert", "George Frederic Handel", "Johann Hummell"]}, "7": {"question": "What larger work is String Quartet K. 387 by Mozart part of?", "correct": "The 'Hayden Quartets'", "incorrect": ["The 'Viennese Quartets'", "Milanese Quartets", "Prussian Quartets"]}, "8": {"question": "How many movements are in String Quartet K. 387 by Mozart?", "correct": "Four", "incorrect": ["Five", "Three", "Six"]}, "9": {"question": "What does 'allegro vivace assai'  mean?", "correct": "Fast and very lively", "incorrect": ["Fast and smooth", "Moderately fast", "Extremely fast and gentle"]}, "10": {"question": "What is the main key of the 1st movement of String Quartet K. 387 by Mozart?", "correct": "G Major", "incorrect": ["D Major", "E Minor", "C Major"]}, "11": {"question": "Which instrument/s plays the main part in the 1st movement of String Quartet K. 387?", "correct": "1st Violin", "incorrect": ["There is no main part - each part has an equal role", "Viola", "1st and 2nd violin"]}, "12": {"question": "Where was Mozart's String Quartet K. 387 composed?", "correct": "Vienna", "incorrect": ["Salzberg", "Innsbruck", "Graz"]}, "13": {"question": "How many String Quartets did Mozart dedicate to Hayden?", "correct": "6", "incorrect": ["4", "8", "2"]}, "14": {"question": "What type of Cadence does the Exposition of the 1st Movement of Mozart's K. 387 end on?", "correct": "Perfect Cadence", "incorrect": ["Interrupted", "Imperfect", "Plagal"]}, "15": {"question": "What order # is String Quartet K. 387 in its larger work?", "correct": "1st", "incorrect": ["6th (Last)", "2nd", "5th"]}, "16": {"question": "How many different clefs are used in Mozart K. 387 mvt 1?", "correct": "3", "incorrect": ["2", "Only 1", "4"]}, "17": {"question": "What is the instrumentation for Mozart's 1st Movement of String Quartet K. 387?", "correct": "Violin 1, Violin 2, Viola, and Cello", "incorrect": ["Violin, Viola, Cello, Double Bass", "Piano and voice", "Violin 1, Violin 2 and Cello", "Piano, Violin, Viola, Cello"]}, "18": {"question": "How many instrumental parts are in 1st Movement of String Quartet K. 387?", "correct": "4", "incorrect": ["5", "3", "6"]}, "19": {"question": "What is the standard instrumentation of the String quartet?", "correct": "Violin 1, Violin 2, Viola, and Cello", "incorrect": ["Violin, Cello 1, Cello 2, and Double Bass", "Violin, Viola, Cello, and Double Bass", "Violin, Viola 1, Viola 2, and Double Bass"]}, "20": {"question": "What was the time span of the classical period?", "correct": "c. 1750 - 1800", "incorrect": ["c. 1700 - 1800", "c. 1650 - 1800", "c. 1500 - 1600"]}, "21": {"question": "What are the main sections in sonata form?", "correct": "Exposition, Development and Recapitulation", "incorrect": ["Beginning, middle and end", "Introduction, Interlude and Exposition", "Exposition, Interlude and Recapitulation "]}, "22": {"question": "When were the Haydn Quartets composed?", "correct": "1782 - 1785", "incorrect": ["1762 - 1770", "2020 - 2022", "1723 - 1725"]}, "23": {"question": "Where were the Haydn Quartets composed?", "correct": "Vienna, Austria", "incorrect": ["London, England", "New York, USA", "Sydney, Australia"]}, "24": {"question": "When did Haydn himself listen to the 6 Haydn Quartets?", "correct": "In 1785", "incorrect": ["In 1775", "In 1995", "In 1786", "Tomorrow"]}, "25": {"question": "What were the Haydn Quartets composed in response to?", "correct": "Haydn - Op. 33 set", "incorrect": ["Haydn - Cello Concerto No. 1", "Haydn - Trumpet Concerto", "Haydn - Symphony No. 94"]}, "26": {"question": " At the time of the development of the String Quartet, what did it provide to wealthy individuals and families?", "correct": "Opportunities for private entertainment", "incorrect": ["Free performances", "Better performers to listen to than in normal public concerts", "More inspiration for them to write songs"]}, "27": {"question": "Why were string quartet performances suitable for private entertainment?", "correct": "It only requires 4 players and a small space for them to play in.", "incorrect": ["Many people played in String Quartets at the time, which meant that many people could recieve private entertainment", "String Quartet Performances were very short which meant it was cheap for private entertainment ", "1 person could play all four parts at once so you only needed to hire one person to play"]}, "28": {"question": "What is the piece format of a typical string quartet?", "correct": "Fast movement, Slow Movement, Minuet and trio and the Fast Finale", "incorrect": ["Minuet and Trio, Slow Movement, Fast Movement and Fast Finale", "Introduction, Fast Movement, Slow Movement and Fast Finale", "There is not a typical Structure for a four movement piece"]}, "29": {"question": "What opportunity did String Quartets give composers?", "correct": "A great range of expressive possibilities", "incorrect": ["To make more money as writing String Quartet pieces were easy to compose", "An opportunity to become famous", "To make music that sounded like rock music"]}, "30": {"question": "Where did string quartets first appear?", "correct": "Southern Germany, Austria and Bohemia", "incorrect": ["England", "Slovakia", "Western Russia"]}, "31": {"question": "By about when had the String Quartet been consolidated into its classical format?", "correct": "About 1780", "incorrect": ["1995", "2020", "1770"]}, "32": {"question": "What was Mozart's father's name?", "correct": "Leopold", "incorrect": ["Gerald", "Frederick", "Johann"]}, "33": {"question": "Who said 'Before God, and as an honest man, I tell you that your son is the greatest composer known to me either in person or by name.' to Mozart's Father, Leopold?", "correct": "Haydn", "incorrect": ["Hummel", "Mozart", "Himself"]}, "34": {"question": "Where was Mozart's father, Leopold, at the time Haydn heard the Haydn quartets?", "correct": "Salzburg", "incorrect": ["Finland", "Rome", "Munich"]}, "35": {"question": "How many main sections are there in sonata form?", "correct": "3", "incorrect": ["4", "2", "6"]}, "36": {"question": "What does op. mean?", "correct": "Opus", "incorrect": ["Over powered", "Operation", "Original piece"]}, "37": {"question": "What op. number did Mozart publish the Haydn Quartets as?", "correct": "Op. 10", "incorrect": ["Op. 11", "Op. 4", "Op. 103"]}, "38": {"question": "What is the general role of the development section (of the Mozart Set Work)?", "correct": "To modulate through a range of keys, while eventually working its way back to the tonic key.", "incorrect": ["To entertain the audience using a variety of note values", "To establish the general mood of the piece"]}, "39": {"question": "What is a subordinate theme?", "correct": "It is the ending of a section or part.", "incorrect": ["A theme within a theme", "A short phrase that is played in another key signature", "The part leading up to the climax of the piece"]}, "40": {"question": "How many players are there in a String Quartet?", "correct": "4", "incorrect": ["6", "5", "2"]}, "41": {"question": "What is a large-scale instrumental genre?", "correct": "A genre that requires a large number of people to play.", "incorrect": ["A genre that requires people to play extrememly large instruments.", "A genre that often includes practise scales in its music.", "A genre in which its musical pieces are of a long duration"]}, "42": {"question": "What phrase can you use to refer to more than one subordinate theme?", "correct": "A Subordinate theme group", "incorrect": ["Subordinate themes", "Subordinate theme cycle", "Sub-cycle"]}, "43": {"question": "The cello can use multiple clefs, but which clef does it use in Mozart's 1st Movement of String Quartet K. 387?", "correct": "Bass Clef", "incorrect": ["Tenor Clef", "Alto clef", "Treble Clef"]}, "44": {"question": "What is the time signature in the 1st Movement of String Quartet K. 387 by Mozart?", "correct": "4/4", "incorrect": ["2/2", "6/4", "3/2"]}, "45": {"question": "What are codettas?", "correct": "A series of cadence-like gestures.", "incorrect": ["The symbol used on sheet music that show you need to go to the coda", "Codetta bake shop (there's one in the US)", "Sheet music symbols that indicate a composition for two performers"]}, "46": {"question": "In Mozart's 1st movement of String Quartet K. 387, only one instrument/part plays in the anacrusis. Which instrument/part is this?", "correct": " Violin 1", "incorrect": ["Cello", "Double Bass", "Violin 2"]}, "47": {"question": "What is an Antecedent phrase?", "correct": "A phrase, usually 4 bars, that precedes the consequent phrase.", "incorrect": ["The phrase that leads into the next section of the piece.", "It is a phrase that is repeated throughout the piece", "A phrase that modulates to another key for a short period of time"]}, "48": {"question": "What are the two different variations of the exposition that could be used in the recapitulation called?", "correct": "Decorative and Structural", "incorrect": ["Sarabande and Minuet", "Decorative and Formal", "Structural and Minuet"]}, "49": {"question": "How many quartets in the set of 6 by Haydn (as Op. 33 in 1781) follow the typical classical format of a piece in four movements?", "correct": "All of them", "incorrect": ["2", "None. The format didn't exist when the quartets were published.", "Only the First and Last"]}, "50": {"question": "Haydn's Op. 33, the set of six quartets, are often reffered to as what?", "correct": "The 'Russian' quartets", "incorrect": ["The Royal Quartets", "The Grand Quartets", "It wasn't refered as to anything."]}, "51": {"question": "Who did Haydn dedicate his Op. 33 set to?", "correct": "The Grand Duke Paul of Russia", "incorrect": ["Mozart", "Schumann", "Schubert"]}, "52": {"question": "First subject' and 'Second subject', or 'primary theme' and 'secondary theme' are other names for what?", "correct": "The 'Main theme' and 'subordinate theme' in Sonata Form.", "incorrect": ["Main theme', and 'antecedent' and 'consequent' phrase", "The Development section", "A phrase that modulates to another key for a short period of time"]}, "53": {"question": "What is a sequence?", "correct": "A passage repeated at a higher or lower pitch.", "incorrect": ["A passage repeated at the same pitch", "A passage repeated at the same pitch, but using different note values", "A passage repeated using randomised pitches"]}, "54": {"question": "Typically, how many bars do antecedent and consequent phrases each last for?", "correct": "4 bars each", "incorrect": ["6 bars", "3 bars", "2 bars"]}, "55": {"question": "How many quatrains does FrÃ¼hingstraum contain?", "correct": "6", "incorrect": ["4", "8", "12"]}}